Guide to the George P. Hall & Son Photograph Collection [1876-1914] PR 24
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
- Series I: Photographs of Manhattan
  - Commercial Buildings - Mounted
    - National Bank of Commerce, 31 Nassau [copy of rendering by Hughson Hawley], [1905] (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - New York Clearing House, 77 Cedar Street (3), [1905], 1913 (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - New York Life Insurance Co., 346-348 Broadway, [1900] (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - New York Stock Exchange [new], 18 Broad Street, 1904 (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - New York Stock Exchange [old], 10 Broad Street, [1890-1901] (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - North America Trust Co. Building, undated (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - Park Bank, [1900]-1914 (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - Presbyterian Building, 156 Fifth Avenue, undated (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - Pulitzer Building [World Building], [1903]-1914 (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - Singer Building, 149 Broadway, [1907-1910], undated (Box 8, Folder 67)
    - Times Building, Times Square (3), 1905 (Box 8, Folder 68)
    - Times Building, Tract Building, Park Row, [1900] (Box 8, Folder 68)
    - Trinity Building, 1908 (Box 8, Folder 68)
    - Trust Company of America Building, Wall and William Streets, 1908 (Box 8, Folder 68)
    - Union Trust Co. of New York, 80 Broadway (2), 1897, undated (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - United States Express Building, Church Street, undated (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - U.S. Rubber co. Building [copy photograph of architectural rendering by Carrere & Hastings], undated (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - E.H. Van Ingen & Co. Building [The Mohawk], Fifth Avenue, undated (Box 8, Folder 70)
    - Ward Line Building, 1904 (Box 8, Folder 70)
    - Washington Life Insurance Building, 141 Broadway, [1900] (Box 8, Folder 70)
    - Welles Building [Seaboard National Bank], 18 Broadway (3), [1905] (Box 8, Folder 71)
    - West Street Building, 90 West Street, 1907 (Box 8, Folder 71)
    - Western National Bank, 13 Nassau Street, [1900] (Box 8, Folder 71)
    - Whitehall Building (2), 1903, undated (Box 9, Folder 72)
    - John Wolfe Building, [1910] (Box 9, Folder 73)
    - Wool Exchange, West Broadway and Beach Street, [1905] (Box 9, Folder 73)
    - Woolworth Building, undated (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - Hotels - Unmounted
    - Academy Hotel and entrance to Oyster House, undated (Box 9, Folder 74)
    - Hotel Algonquin, West 44th Street, undated (Box 9, Folder 74)
    - Appleton House, undated (Box 9, Folder 74)
    - Hotel Astor, Broadway and 45th Streets, undated (Box 9, Folder 74)
    - Astor House [copy photograph of watercolor], undated (Box 9, Folder 74)
    - Astor House, interiors (3), undated (Box 9, Folder 74)
    - Hotel Bartholdi, Broadway and 23rd Street, undated (Box 9, Folder 74)
    - Hotel Belleclaire, Broadway and 77th Street, [1910] (Box 9, Folder 74)
    - Breslin Hotel, Broadway and 29th Street, undated (Box 9, Folder 74)
    - Cadillac Hotel, Broadway and 43rd Street, undated (Box 9, Folder 74)
    - Courte Hotel, Broadway and 21st Street, undated (Box 9, Folder 74)
    - Hotel Gallatin, undated (Box 9, Folder 74)
    - Herald Square Hotel, undated (Box 9, Folder 74)
    - Hotel Laurelton, undated (Box 9, Folder 75)
    - Hotel Manhattan, undated (Box 9, Folder 75)
    - Hotel Marie Antoinette, undated (Box 9, Folder 75)
    - Hotel McAlpin, 34th Street and Fifth Avenue, undated (Box 9, Folder 75)
    - Mills Hotel and extension, interior and exteriors (3), undated (Box 9, Folder 75)
    - Mills House, Bleecker Street, undated (Box 9, Folder 75)
    - Hotel Monticello, undated (Box 9, Folder 75)
    - New Grand Hotel, undated (Box 9, Folder 75)
    - Park Avenue Hotel, undated (Box 9, Folder 76)
    - Plaza Hotel, Fift Avenue, 58th and 59th Streets, undated (Box 9, Folder 76)
    - Prince George Hotel, undated (Box 9, Folder 76)
    - Hotel St. Denis, Broadway and 11th Streets (2), undated (Box 9, Folder 76)
    - St. Nicholas Hotel [copy photograph], undated (Box 9, Folder 76)
    - Hotel Savoy, [1905] (Box 9, Folder 76)
    - Spingler House, Union Square [copy photograph of halftone], undated (Box 9, Folder 76)
    - U.S. Hotel, Water Street, undated (Box 9, Folder 76)
    - Hotel Victoria, undated (Box 9, Folder 76)
    - Waldorf-Astoria Hotel, undated (Box 9, Folder 76)
    - West Shore Hotel, undated (Box 9, Folder 76)
    - Westminster Hotel, undated (Box 9, Folder 76)
    - Unidentified Hotel interior, cashier's cage and lobby, undated (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - Hotels - Mounted
    - Albemarle and Hoffman House Hotels (2), [1904], undated (Box 9, Folder 77)
    - Hotel Astor, [1905] (Box 9, Folder 77)
    - Astor House (2), 1905 (Box 9, Folder 77)
    - Hotel Belmont (2), 1906, 1911 (Box 9, Folder 78)
    - Hotel Beresford, Central Park West and 81st Street, [1905] (Box 9, Folder 78)
    - Broadway Central Hotel, 665-675 Broadway, undated (Box 9, Folder 78)
    - Buckingham Hotel, [1905] (Box 9, Folder 78)
    - Claremont Inn, garden and nearby Grant's Tomb (3), undated (Box 9, Folder 79)
    - Fifth Avenue Hotel, undated (Box 9, Folder 79)
    - Gilsey House, [1903] (Box 10, Folder 80)
    - Holland House, Fifth Avenue at 30th Street, undated (Box 10, Folder 80)
    - Hotel Marie Antoinette, undated (Box 10, Folder 81)
    - Marlborough Hotel, Broadway and 36th Street, [1905] (Box 10, Folder 81)
    - HOtel Martha Washington, East 29th Street, undated (Box 10, Folder 81)
    - Hotel Netherland, Fifth Avenue and 59th Street (2), [1905] (Box 10, Folder 82)
    - Plaza Hotel, undated (Box 10, Folder 82)
    - Hotel Savoy, [1905] (Box 10, Folder 82)
    - Vendome Hotel, Broadway and 41st Street, undated (Box 10, Folder 83)
    - Waldorf-Astoria Hotel, [1893-1905] (Box 10, Folder 83)
  - Public Buildings and Institutions - Unmounted
    - American Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Animals, undated (Box 10, Folder 84)
    - Appellate Court, 24th Street and Madison Avenue, undated (Box 10, Folder 84)
    - Armories (11), undated (Box 10, Folder 84)
    - Catholic Club, 120 Central Park South, [1871-1890] (Box 10, Folder 85)
    - Chamber of Commerce, Liberty Street, [1905] (Box 10, Folder 85)
    - Chemists' Club Building, 50-52 East 41st Street, undated (Box 10, Folder 85)
    - City College of New York (3), [1910], undated (Box 10, Folder 85)
    - City Hall, 1 decorated for Admiral Dewey Parade? (3), [1898], undated (Box 10, Folder 85)
    - Columbia College [Columbia University] and Barnard College, interiors (22), undated (Box 10, Folder 86-87)
    - Columbia College [Columbia University] and Barnard College, exteriors (20), undated (Box 10, Folder 88-89)
    - Convent of the Sacred Heart, 133rd and Convent Avenue, undated (Box 10, Folder 90)
    - Cooper Union for the Advancement of Science and Art, undated (Box 10, Folder 90)
    - Ellis Island Immigration Station, undated (Box 11, Folder 91)
    - Federal Hall (2), undated (Box 11, Folder 91)
    - Fraunces Tavern, undated (Box 11, Folder 91)
    - French Hospital [Hopital Francais], undated (Box 11, Folder 91)
    - Grace Institute, undated (Box 11, Folder 91)
    - Grand Central Terminal, undated (Box 11, Folder 91)
    - Hall of Records, 1 during demolition (3), [1907], undated (Box 11, Folder 91)
    - Hardware Club, interiors (2), undated (Box 11, Folder 91)
    - Lincoln Hospital, undated (Box 11, Folder 92)
    - Lotus Club, 556-558 Fifth Avenue, [1900] (Box 11, Folder 92)
    - Lying-in Hospital, Second Avenue and 17th Street, undated (Box 11, Folder 92)
    - Morgan Library, East 36th Street, undated (Box 11, Folder 92)
    - The New-York Historical Society, 1907 (Box 11, Folder 93)
    - New York Municipal Building (2), 1914, undated (Box 11, Folder 93)
    - New York Public Library, Fifth Avenue and 42nd Street, lions and facade, undated (Box 11, Folder 93)
    - New York Public Library, Seventh Avenue branch, undated (Box 11, Folder 93)
    - Orphan Asylum Society of the City of New York, undated (Box 11, Folder 93)
    - Pennsylvania Station, interiors and 1 exterior, 1910-1911, undated (Box 11, Folder 94)
    - Polyclinic Hospital, undated (Box 11, Folder 95)
    - Polo Grounds, Harlem River at 157th Street, undated (Box 11, Folder 95)
    - Public Baths, undated (Box 11, Folder 95)
    - Tammany Hall, East 14th Street, 1904 (Box 11, Folder 95)
    - Theological Seminary, Tenth Avenue and 20th Street, undated (Box 11, Folder 95)
    - Union Club, Fifth Avenue and 51st Street, undated (Box 11, Folder 96)
    - Union League Club, Fifth Avenue at 39th Street, 1 interior (2), undated (Box 11, Folder 96)
    - Union Theological Seminary, West 120th-122nd Streets, [1910] (Box 11, Folder 96)
    - United States Custom House, undated (Box 11, Folder 96)
    - United States Post Office, Eighth Avenue and 33rd Street, undated (Box 11, Folder 96)
  - Public Buildings and Institutions - Mounted
    - American Museum of Natural History, undated (Box 11, Folder 97)
    - Art Students League, 215 West 57th Street, [1905] (Box 11, Folder 97)
    - Babies Hospital, 659 Lexington at 55th Street, undated (Box 11, Folder 98)
    - Belleview Hospital, [1905] (Box 11, Folder 98)
    - Castle Clinton [Castle Garden], undated (Box 11, Folder 99)
    - Castle William, Governors Island, undated (Box 11, Folder 99)
    - Chamber of Commerce, entrance and sculpture groups, [1901] (Box 11, Folder 99)
    - Children's Farm School, looking across Hudson River, undated (Box 11)
    - City Hall, from Park Row, [1905] (Box 11, Folder 100)
    - City College of New York, Lexington Avenue at 23rd Street, undated (Box 11, Folder 100)
    - Columbia University (4), 1898-[1910] (Box 12, Folder 101)
    - Criminal Courts Building, Centre Street, 1904 (Box 12, Folder 102)
    - Ellis Island Immigration Station, 1903 (Box 12, Folder 102)
    - Grand Central Terminal, 1899 (Box 12, Folder 103)
    - Hall of Records, Centre Street, 1904 (Box 12, Folder 103)
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1909, undated (Box 12, Folder 104)
    - Municipal Building, Centre and Chambers Streets, [1914] (Box 12, Folder 105)
    - New York University, [1905] (Box 12, Folder 105)
    - Pennsylvania station, excavation site (2), [1903] (Box 12, Folder 106)
    - Sloane Maternity Hospital, undated (Box 12, Folder 107)
    - South Ferry Terminal, [1905] (Box 12, Folder 107)
    - The Tombs [New York City Prison], 1904 (Box 12, Folder 107)
    - Tweed Court House, Chambers Street, [1905] (Box 12, Folder 107)
    - U.S. Post Office, Broadway and Park Row (2), [1910], undated (Box 12, Folder 108)
  - Residences - Unmounted
    - Brownstones, unidentified (2), undated (Box 12, Folder 109)
    - William A. Clark mansion, 77th Street and Fifth Avenue, [1904-1914] (Box 12, Folder 109)
    - Helen Gould residence, Fifth Avenue, undated (Box 12, Folder 109)
    - Gramercy Square, 2-4, west side, undated (Box 12, Folder 109)
    - Jumel Mansion, undated (Box 12, Folder 109)
    - Lafayette Terrace Apartments, undated (Box 12, Folder 109)
    - Stern residence, 993 Fifth Avenue, undated (Box 12, Folder 109)
    - Tiffany mansion, Madison Avenue and 72nd Street, undated (Box 12, Folder 109)
  - Residences - Mounted
    - John D. Crimmins residence, 40 East 68th Street, undated (Box 12, Folder 110)
    - Osborne Apartments, 57th Street and Fifth Avenue, undated (Box 12, Folder 110)
  - Restaurants - Unmounted
    - Annex Café, Church Street, undated (Box 13, Folder 111)
    - Beaux Arts Café, interior, undated (Box 13, Folder 111)
    - Beer Garden, 42nd Street and Seventh Avenue [above Belasco Theatre, views with farm animals] (2), undated (Box 13, Folder 111)
    - Delmonico's, 44th Street and Fifth Avenue, [1897-1914] (Box 13, Folder 111)
    - Sherry's [private dining room], undated (Box 13, Folder 111)
    - Vienna Hall, 65 Columbia Street, undated (Box 13, Folder 111)
  - Restaurants - Mounted
    - Metropolitan Club, interior, banquet set for Mayor Seth Low, [1901] (Box 13, Folder 112)
  - Statues and Monuments - Unmounted
    - Benjamin Franklin, Park Row, undated (Box 13, Folder 113)
    - Grant's Tomb, Riverside Drive (3), undated (Box 13, Folder 113)
    - Nathan Hale, City Hall Park (2), undated (Box 13, Folder 113)
    - Garret Augustus Hobart, undated (Box 13, Folder 113)
    - Abraham Lincoln, Union Square, undated (Box 13, Folder 113)
    - Maine Monument, Central Park West and Columbus Circle, undated (Box 13, Folder 114)
    - William Tecumseh Sherman equestrian by St Gaudens, between 59th and 60th Streets on Fifth Avenue, undated (Box 13, Folder 114)
    - Soldiers and Sailors Monument, Riverside Drive (3), undated (Box 13, Folder 114)
    - Washington Arch, Washington Square Park, undated (Box 13, Folder 114)
    - Giovanni da Verrazzano, Battery Park, undated (Box 13, Folder 114)
  - Statues and Monuments - Mounted
    - David G. Farragut by St Gaudens, Madison Square, [1905] (Box 13, Folder 115)
    - Grant's Tomb and Claremont Inn, Riverside Drive, 1910 (Box 13, Folder 115)
    - Richard Morris Hunt, Fifth Avenue, 69th and 70th Streets, [1905] (Box 13, Folder 115)
    - General William Tecumseh Sherman equestrian statue, Fifth Avenue and 59th Street (3), [1905] (Box 13, Folder 116)
    - Soldiers and Sailors Monument, Riverside Drive (3), [1902], undated (Box 13, Folder 117)
    - Statue of Liberty (5), 1898, 1903, undated (Box 13, Folder 118)
    - Washington Arch, Washington Square, undated (Box 13, Folder 119)
  - Street Scenes - Unmounted
    - Named Streets (includes parks and squares)
      - Battery Park (2), undated (Box 14, Folder 120)
      - Bowling Green (2), 1908, undated (Box 14, Folder 120)
      - Bridge Street, undated (Box 14, Folder 120)
      - Broad Street, including Fraunces Tavern (5), 1895-1913, undated (Box 14, Folder 120)
      - Broadway, 18, near Battery Place, undated (Box 14, Folder 121)
      - Broadway and Liberty Street, Singer and Bourne Buildings, 1896 (Box 14, Folder 121)
      - Broadway, 203, Mail and Express Building, undated (Box 14, Folder 121)
      - Broadway, looking north from 205, undated (Box 14, Folder 121)
      - Broadway, 212, George P. Hall & Son Photography Studio, interior and exterior (2), [1901-1914] (Box 14, Folder 121)
      - Broadway, 261-267, across from City Hall Park, undated (Box 14, Folder 121)
      - Broadway, City Hall and City Hall Park, undated (Box 14, Folder 121)
      - Broadway, 350, undated (Box 14, Folder 121)
      - Broadway, 401, Chicago, Rock Island, and Pacific Railroad Ticket Office, undated (Box 14, Folder 121)
      - Broadway, 419, Hanan & Son Shoe Store, undated (Box 14, Folder 121)
      - Broadway, North from Spring Street, showing Worth Monument, undated (Box 14, Folder 122)
      - Broadway, North from Bond Street [copy of 1867 photograph by Mathew Brady], undated (Box 14, Folder 122)
      - Broadway and 3rd Street, Monk's Signs storefront, undated (Box 14, Folder 122)
      - Broadway, 920, Denzer Bros. Real Estate, undated (Box 14, Folder 122)
      - Broadway at 23rd Street, Heinz 57 signboard, Pach Bros. studio in background, undated (Box 14, Folder 122)
      - Broadway at 26th Street, undated (Box 14, Folder 122)
      - Broadway, looking north from 27th Street, with Hotel Victoria in foreground, undated (Box 14, Folder 122)
      - Broadway, north from 32nd Street, Herald Square, elevated railroad station, undated (Box 14, Folder 122)
      - Broadway, 1254, including Hotel Imperial and Union Dime Savings Bank, [1909-1914] (Box 14, Folder 122)
      - Broadway and 34th Street, corner building surrounded by R.H. Macy & Co., undated (Box 14, Folder 122)
      - Broadway, north of Times Square, undated (Box 14, Folder 122)
      - Broadway and 110th Street, undated (Box 14, Folder 122)
      - Broadway at 145th Street, undated (Box 14, Folder 122)
      - Broome Street, 510, [1915] (Box 14, Folder 123)
      - Bryant Park and statue of William Cullen Bryant, undated (Box 14, Folder 123)
      - Bryant Park, looking toward Aeolian Hall, undated (Box 14, Folder 123)
      - Central Park South, showing trolleys, undated (Box 14, Folder 123)
      - Centre Street, Hall of Records, Municipal Building, undated (Box 14, Folder 123)
      - Chrystie Street, 3-7, including slum buildings, undated (Box 14, Folder 123)
      - Cooper Square (2 copies), 1909 (Box 14, Folder 123)
      - Cortlandt Street, undated (Box 14, Folder 123)
      - Fulton Street, Fulton Fish Market, undated (Box 14, Folder 123)
      - Fulton Street, 28-30, including S.A. Brown Pharmacy, undated (Box 14, Folder 123)
      - Fulton Street, 78, George P. Hall storefront, [1876-1883] (Box 14, Folder 123)
      - Fulton Street, 157, George P. Hall & Son storefront (2), [1883-1901] (Box 14, Folder 123)
      - Greenwich Avenue, undated (Box 14, Folder 124)
      - Hanover Square, elevated railroad tracks between buildings, undated (Box 14, Folder 124)
      - Harlem Speedway, undated (Box 14, Folder 124)
      - Herald Square (3), [1910], undated (Box 14, Folder 124)
      - John Street, 71-77 (2), undated (Box 14, Folder 124)
      - Lafayette Street at Howard, including Star Café, undated (Box 14, Folder 124)
      - Madison Avenue and 36th Street, northeast corner, undated (Box 14, Folder 124)
      - Maiden Lane, Taft and Sherman campaign banner, 1908 (Box 14, Folder 124)
      - Mott Street, 7-11 and 12-16, Chinatown views (2), undated (Box 14, Folder 124)
      - Park Avenue and 21st Street, undated (Box 14, Folder 125)
      - Park Avenue looking north from 32nd Street, undated (Box 14, Folder 125)
      - Park Avenue looking south from 42nd Street, undated (Box 14, Folder 125)
      - Park Row (3), undated (Box 14, Folder 125)
      - Park Row and Frankfort Street, "Homeward Bound", 1906 (Box 14, Folder 125)
      - Pearl and Beaver Streets, elevated railroad, undated (Box 14, Folder 125)
      - Pell Street, Chinatown, undated (Box 14, Folder 125)
      - Reade Street, 88-90, Webster Manufacturing Co., undated (Box 14, Folder 125)
      - Reade Street and Centre Street, Hall of Records with demolition for Municipal Building in foreground, [1907] (Box 14, Folder 125)
      - South Street, 23, undated (Box 14, Folder 125)
      - South Street, 79-82, at Fletcher Street after a fire, winter, undated (Box 14, Folder 125)
      - South Street, ships, undated (Box 14, Folder 125)
      - State Street, 1-7, including Seaman's Church Institute, undated (Box 14, Folder 125)
      - State Street, 5-12, from Battery Park, undated (Box 14, Folder 125)
      - Union Square (8), 1910, undated (Box 14, Folder 126)
      - Varick Street, 218-228, including A. Benetti, undated (Box 14, Folder 126)
      - Vesey Street, 12-18, undated (Box 14, Folder 126)
      - Wall Street (6), undated (Box 14, Folder 126)
      - Water Street, 188, Bruce & Cook Sheet Iron, undated (Box 14, Folder 126)
      - West Street, Chelsea Docks, Piers 55-61, [1910] (Box 14, Folder 126)
      - Whitehall Street, looking north to Bowling Green, undated (Box 14, Folder 126)
      - William Street, 84, Royal Insurance Building, [1910] (Box 14, Folder 126)
      - William Street, bird's-eye view, undated (Box 14, Folder 126)
      - Unidentified construction and street view, undated (Box 14, Folder 126)
    - Numbered Avenues
      - Fifth Avenue and 23rd Street, Madison Square (2), [1910], undated (Box 14, Folder 127)
      - Fifth Avenue and 26th Street, Washington Centennial Arch and Parade [copy photograph], 1889 Apr. 30 (Box 14, Folder 127)
      - Fifth Avenue and 30th Street, Vanderbilt and Peacock Coaches in front of Holland House, undated (Box 14, Folder 127)
      - Fifth Avenue at 42nd Street, looking north (2 copies), 1909 (Box 14, Folder 127)
      - Fifth Avenue at 46th Street, Windsor Arcade, [1905] (Box 14, Folder 127)
      - Fifth Avenue looking north from 49th Street, St. Patrick's Cathedral towers and facade, undated (Box 14, Folder 127)
      - Fifth Avenue and 51st Street, Vanderbilt Houses, undated (Box 14, Folder 127)
      - Fifth Avenue north above 53rd Street, undated (Box 14, Folder 127)
      - Fifth Avenue and 61st Street, rooftop view to north, [1904] (Box 14, Folder 127)
      - Sixth Avenue and 14th Street, elevated railroad station, undated (Box 14, Folder 128)
      - Sixth Avenue south from 23rd to 18th Street, undated (Box 14, Folder 128)
      - Sixth Avenue and 41st Street, undated (Box 14, Folder 128)
      - Eighth Avenue and 59th Street, southwest corner, undated (Box 14, Folder 128)
      - Ninth Avenue and 15th Street, with elevated railroad, [1908] (Box 14, Folder 128)
    - Numbered Streets
      - 23rd Street at Ninth Avenue, undated (Box 14, Folder 129)
      - 23rd Street at Broadway, looking east toward Metropolitan Life Building and Madison Square, undated (Box 14, Folder 129)
      - West 23rd Street, 32-36, Stern Brothers [copy photograph of a lithograph], undated (Box 14, Folder 129)
      - West 29th Street, 536-8, Young Brothers & Boss Co., undated (Box 14, Folder 129)
      - West 34th Street, 47, Marbridge Building, undated (Box 14, Folder 129)
      - 42nd Street and Vanderbilt Avenue, James A. Hetherington Pharmacy (2), [1912] (Box 14, Folder 129)
      - undated (Box 14, Folder 129)
      - 42nd Street and Depew Place, undated (Box 14, Folder 129)
      - 125th Street near Broadway, viaduct, undated (Box 14, Folder 129)
      - West 149th Street, 460, [1912] (Box 14, Folder 129)
  - Street Scenes - Mounted
    - Named Streets (includes parks and squares)
      - Ann Street at Nassau Street, 1904 (Box 15, Folder 130)
      - Battery Place, 1903 (Box 15, Folder 130)
      - Bowery, north from Grand Street, 1903 (Box 15, Folder 130)
      - Bowling Green, with excavation for Customs House, [1904] (Box 15, Folder 131)
      - Bowling Green, from south, [1905] (Box 15, Folder 131)
      - Broad Street, with New York Stock Exchange (4), [1903]-1912 (Box 15, Folder 132)
      - Broad Street, "Curb Brokers", [1912] (Box 15)
      - Broadway, 26-44, Standard Oil and Hudson Buildings, [1905] (Box 15, Folder 133)
      - Broadway, 42 (2 copies), [1905] (Box 15, Folder 133)
      - Broadway, 64-80, Union Trust Company and Manhattan Life Insurance Company, undated (Box 15, Folder 133)
      - Broadway, 182-200 northeast corner of John Street, undated (Box 15, Folder 134)
      - Broadway, 198-204, undated (Box 15, Folder 134)
      - Broadway, 201-207, [1905] (Box 15, Folder 134)
      - Broadway, 290-304, 1903 (Box 15, Folder 134)
      - Broadway at 22nd Street, including Flatiron Building, undated (Box 15, Folder 134)
      - Broadway and Barclay Street, The Hub [clothier], undated (Box 15, Folder 135)
      - Broadway south from Cedar Street, U.S. Realty Buiding, 1908 (Box 15, Folder 135)
      - Broadway and Chambers Street (5), [1905-1910], undated (Box 15, Folder 136)
      - Broadway and Fifth Avenue, looking north, 1898 (Box 15, Folder 137)
      - Broadway and Franklin Street, [1905] (Box 15, Folder 137)
      - Broadway, looking south from Liberty Street, [1905] (Box 15, Folder 137)
      - Broadway, looking north from Murray Street, 1909 (Box 15, Folder 137)
      - Broadway and Park Row, [1905] (Box 15, Folder 138)
      - Broadway, rooftop view looking north at Trinity spire, undated (Box 15, Folder 138)
      - Lower Broadway [copy of architectural rendering], [1905] (Box 15, Folder 138)
      - Centre Street, looking north from excavation site for Municipal Building, [1905] (Box 16, Folder 139)
      - Chatham Square, elevated railroad, [1900] (Box 16, Folder 139)
      - Church Street, looking southwest from rooftop (2 copies), [1910] (Box 16, Folder 139)
      - City Hall Park (7), [1903-1910], undated (Box 16, Folder 140-141)
      - Columbus Circle, during subway construction, [1895] (Box 16, Folder 142)
      - Columbus Circle (2), undated (Box 16, Folder 142)
      - Dey Street, 38, [1900] (Box 16, Folder 142)
      - Front Street and Coenties Slip, undated (Box 16, Folder 143)